(Penny:)Oh. That's so sweet.
(Penny:)But I'm going out dancing
with a girlfriend.
You can't go out, it's "Halo" night.
(Penny:)Well, for Penny, it's dancing night.
- You go dancing every Wednesday?
- No.
(Sheldon:)Then it's not dancing night.
Why don't I play with you tomorrow?
Tonight is "Halo" night.
It's like talking to a wall.
All right, now, Sheldon,
you and I are about to have a problem.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, remember, we role-played this.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but you didn't portray her
as completely irrational.
All right, fellas, I gotta go.
But good luck.
Maybe we should've asked if we could go
dancing with her and her girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)Okay, assuming we could dance,
which we can't...
(Sheldon:)...there are three of us and two of them.
(Penny:)- So?
- It's the Chinese restaurant all over again.
(Sheldon:)I assure you that cutting
a dumpling in thirds is child's play...
(Sheldon:)...compared with three men each attempting
to dance with 67 percent of a woman.